Guide to the Artists Space Collection of Artist Files MSS.506
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Oakes, Julie, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Oates, Leah, 2001-2004 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Obando, Pierre, 2001-2005 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Obarzanek, Simon, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Obata, Etsuko, 1996 (Box 62, Folder 52)
- Obaza, Susan, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Oberst, Carolyn, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Obuchoska, Linda, 1999-2001 (Box 40, Folder 14)
- Ochiai, Tam, 1992 (Box 62, Folder 52)
- Offill-Klein, Alison, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 16)
- Oh, Michael Euyung, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 17)
- Okada, Katsura, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 18)
- Okamoto, Mitsuhiro, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 19)
- Olano, Beatriz, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 20)
- Olenick, Iviva, 2003-2005 (Box 40, Folder 21)
- Olivier, Karyn, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 22)
- Olivier, Nancy, 1998-2000 (Box 40, Folder 23)
- Olivier, Stephen, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 24)
- Olmer, Adeline, 1985-1989 (Box 62, Folder 50)
- Olsen, Rune, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 25)
- Olshansky, Mark, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 26)
- Olson, Christine, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 27)
- Olson, Nina, 1987-1996 (Box 40, Folder 28)
- Ondrus, Christina, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 30)
- Onnen, Serge, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 31)
- Oppenheimer, Sarah, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 32)
- Oppermann, Julie, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 33)
- Oransky, Howard, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 34)
- Oratofsky, Paul, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 35)
- Ordway, Lois, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 36)
- Orfescu, Cris, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 37)
- Orjuela, Lisie, 2003-2006 (Box 40, Folder 38)
- Ormezzano, Florence, 1998 (Box 62, Folder 49)
- Oros, Mary, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 39)
- Ortega, Raul, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 41)
- Osborne, Jen, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 42)
- Oscherwitz, Steven J., 2003 (Box 40, Folder 43)
- Osgood, Susan, 1994-2001 (Box 40, Folder 44)
- Oshima, Mari, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 47)
- Oshman, Anne, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 48)
- Osip, Sandra, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 49)
- Osman, Jim, 1999-2001 (Box 40, Folder 50)
- Ostrowitz, Judith, 1990-1998 (Box 40, Folder 51)
- Otani, Hideo, 2000 (Box 64, Folder 45)
- Ott, Jacqueline, 1995 (Box 40, Folder 52)
- Outlaw, Adrienne, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 53)
- Ouwerkerk, Sarah Van, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 58)
- Ovchinnikov, Valeriy, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 54)
- Overbay, Paula, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 55)
- Owen, Barbara, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 56)
- Owen, Michael, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 57)
- Owens, Rachel, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 58)
- Oyarbide, Vivian, 2003-2004 (Box 40, Folder 59)
- Paasch, Robert, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 60)
- Pacheco, Mark, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 61)
- Pagano, Alfonse, 1986-1989 (Box 62, Folder 57)
- Pagnucco, Jayne, 1999 (Box 64, Folder 46)
- Pais, Ines, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 62)
- Paker, Ozlem, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 63)
- Palaia, Franc, 1991-1993 (Box 62, Folder 56)
- Palazzolo, Francis, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 64)
- Palermo, Stephen, 1994-2004 (Box 40, Folder 65)
- Palmer, Camilla, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 66)
- Palmer, Jane, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 67)
- Palmer, Kristen, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 68)
- Palmer, Laura H, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 69)
- Palmer, Marcy, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 70)
- Palmerton, Elwyn, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 71)
- Palumbo, Michael, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 72)
- Paneth, Thea, 1990-1992 (Box 62, Folder 55)
- Paolozzi, Gianfranco, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 73)
- Papamaechel, Irene, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 74)
- Pape, Sky, 1994-2001 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Paplin, Adam, 1995-1996 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Pappa, Kenneth, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Paradis, Jason, 2000-2001 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- paraiso, virgo, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Pardoe, David, 2002-2004 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Pardue, Kristina, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Pardue, Meredith, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Parga, Frank, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Parise, Stephen, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Parisi, Ronald, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Park, Ae-Young, 2003 (Box 64, Folder 98)
- Park, Chunsoo, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Park, Ga Hae, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 13)
- Parker, John, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 14)
- Parker, Kathy, 2005 (Box 41, Folder 15)
- Parker, Walter Van Eps, undated (Box 56, Folder 31)
- Parlade, Claudio, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 16)
- Parlato, Carolanna, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 17)
- Parris, Bridget, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 18)
- Parsons, Tara, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 19)
- Partee, Bianca, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 20)
- Partegas, Ester, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 21)
- Pasila, Joanne, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 22)
- Pasquarelli, Richard, 1999-2004 (Box 41, Folder 23)
- Pasquini, Stefano, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 24)
- Passarella, Gilbert, 1994-2001 (Box 41, Folder 25)
- Pasternak, Shirley, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 26)
- Pastine, Francesca, 2004-2005 (Box 66, Folder 23)
- Patch, Greg, 2005 (Box 41, Folder 27)
- Patel, Avani, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 28)
- Patti, Anthony, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 29)
- Paul, Joseph, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 30)
- Paul, Katrin, 1993-1994 (Box 62, Folder 54)
- Paul, Linda, 2005 (Box 41, Folder 31)
- Pauley, Steve, 2005 (Box 41, Folder 32)
- Paulson, Douglas, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 33)
- Pavlicovic, Jim, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 34)
- Paxton, Greg, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 35)
- Paz, Alicia, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 36)
- Paz, Manuela, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 37)
- Paz, Sharon, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 38)
- Pearson, Cadence, 1998 (Box 64, Folder 46)
- Pease, Lillian, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 39)
- Peck, Judith, 2005 (Box 41, Folder 40)
- Pecora, Adria, 1999-2002 (Box 41, Folder 41)
- Pedigo, Ian, 2005 (Box 41, Folder 42)
- Pedulla, Albert, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 43)
- Pedziwiatr, Michael, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 44)
- Peer, Leta, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 45)
- Peerna, Jaanika, 2005 (Box 41, Folder 46)
- Pehrson, Mats, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 47)
- Peigelbeck, Magen, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 48)
- Pelaez-Dorian, Linda, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 49)
- Pella, Anibal, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 50)
- Pella, Nicholas, 2005 (Box 41, Folder 51)
- Peller, Joseph, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 52)
- Pelletier, Juliette, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 53)
- Pellettieri, Chris, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 54)
- Pelli, Leemour, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 55)
- Pellicoro, Jon, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 56)
- Peigna, Jean-Marie, 1986-1988 (Box 62, Folder 60)
- Pena, Claudia, 2000-2004 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Pendergast, Joseph, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Penkala, Matthew, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Pentecost, Claire, 1989 (Box 62, Folder 61)
- Perantoni, Ellen, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Percoco, Anne, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Perelman, Luis, 1995-2001 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Perez, Betty, 1986-1998 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Perez, Victoria, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Perez-Ortega, Jose, 1989 (Box 62, Folder 59)
- Perkalis, Charles, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- Perkins, Rowena, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Perrine, Doreen, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- Perrini, Paul, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 12)
- Perry, Alison, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 13)
- Perry, Vicky, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 14)
- Pervil, Abby, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- Pervin, Gilda, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 16)
- Peters, Ed, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 17)
- Peters, Joshua, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 18)
- Peters, Lynn, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 19)
- Petersen, Henrietta, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 20)
- Peterson, Ken, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 21)
- Petker-Mintz, Lisa, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 22)
- Petras, Meghan, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 23)
- Petrick, Robert, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 24)
- Petrov, Andrei, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 25)
- Petrov, Andrei, 1991-1995 (Box 42, Folder 26)
- Petrov, Daniel, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 27)
- Petrovic, Sebastijan, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 28)
- Petruska, Jane, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 29)
- Pettett, Leigha, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 30)
- Pettijohn, Zoe, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 31)
- Peyton, Gaines, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 32)
- Pezalla, Jessica, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 33)
- Pezzella, Rosanna, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 34)
- Pfarr, Theresa, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 35)
- Pfeifer, Joseph, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 36)
- Pham, Nathalie, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 37)
- Phanphiroj, Ohm, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 38)
- Phelps, Danica, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 39)
- Philippides, Birgitte, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 40)
- Phillips, Brian, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 41)
- Phillips, Jonathan, 1994-1996 (Box 42, Folder 42)
- Phillips, Laura Sue, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 43)
- Phillips, Morgan, 1990-1997 (Box 42, Folder 44)
- Phillips, Rachel, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 45)
- Phillips, Sarah, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 46)
- Phillips and Rowley, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 47)
- Pibal, Ann, 1998 (Box 64, Folder 47)
- Picco, Gabriele, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 48)
- Pickerill, Timothy, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 49)
- Piechucki, Melissa, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 50)
- Pierce, Jack, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 51)
- Pilato, Karl, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 52)
- Pile, Winner, 1993 (Box 62, Folder 83)
- Pillorge, Nicole, 1991-2002 (Box 42, Folder 53)
- Pinel, Georges, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 54)
- Pingree, Meridith, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 55)
- Pinon, Dora, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 56)
- Pinto, Mary, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 57)
- Pipi, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 58)
- Pippa, Fiona, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 59)
- Pisoni, Paul, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 60)
- Pitsch, Christina, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 61)
- Pitsker, Paul, 2002-2004 (Box 42, Folder 62)
- Pitt, Adam, 1994-1995 (Box 42, Folder 63)
- Pittman, Gene, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 64)
- Pivetta, Raphaela, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 65)
- Pizzani, Lucia, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 66)
- Plate, Catya, 1997-2002 (Box 42, Folder 67)
- Plesset, Anna, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 68)
- Plimpton, Sarah, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 69)
- Pliskin, Berenice, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 70)
- Pliskin, Ellen, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 71)
- Pochron, Julie, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 72)
- Podemski, Esther, 1988-2001 (Box 42, Folder 73)
- Podlach, Betsy, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Podoll, Joshua, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Podwil, Jonathan, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Poelz, Dorke, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Polance, Joyce, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Polashenski, Anne, 1998-2003 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Polishchuk, Slava, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Pollack, Noah, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Polli, Andrea, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Pollock, Sara, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Polumbo, Randy, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Ponce, Michael, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Pontes, Nuno, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 13)
- Poon, Annie, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 14)
- Pope, Mary Ann, 2001 (Box 43, Folder 15)
- Popov, Milena, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 16)
- Popova, Natalia, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 17)
- Porter, Aaron, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 18)
- Porterfield, Jeff, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 19)
- Posch, Josefina, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 20)
- Potter, Chloe, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 21)
- Potter, William, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 22)
- Powell, Jocelyn, 2004 (Box 64, Folder 97)
- Powers, Devin, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 23)
- Powers, Donna, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 24)
- Powhida, William, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 25)
- Pozzi, Julian, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 26)
- Pozzvoli, Anna, 2001 (Box 64, Folder 48)
- Prange, Chas, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 27)
- Pratt, Suzanne, 2006 (Box 62, Folder 62)
- Pred, Michele, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 28)
- Premnath, Sreshta, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 29)
- Prest, Mel, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 30)
- Preston, Maggie, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 31)
- Preto, Fernanda, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 32)
- Price, Michael, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 33)
- Priddy, Rodney, 2000-2003 (Box 43, Folder 34)
- Priesch, Hannes, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 35)
- Prince, Lily, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 36)
- Productions, Ned and Shiva, 2000-2003 (Box 43, Folder 37)
- Pronin, Anatoly, 1989 (Box 62, Folder 63)
- Pronina, Nadia, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 38)
- Propp, Marilyn, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 39)
- Provenzano, Michelle, 2002-2005 (Box 43, Folder 40)
- Prudhomme, Tedd, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 41)
- Prybolsky, Jeff, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 42)
- Pucciarelli, Vincent, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 43)
- Puckitt, Sarah, 1999 (Box 64, Folder 40)
- Pugh, John, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 44)
- Pugliese, Carol, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 45)
- Pulvermakher, Anna, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 46)
- Pungercar, Marija Mojca, 1988-1997 (Box 43, Folder 47)
- Purdy, Dianne, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 48)
- Puri, Antonio, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 49)
- Puttgen, Julie, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 50)
- Pyle, Amy, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 51)
- Pyle, Ellie, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 52)
- Pyle, Kevin C., 1988-1993 (Box 62, Folder 84)
- Pyle, Timothy, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 53)
- Quaresma, Julio, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 54)
- Quinn, Exton, 1994-1997 (Box 64, Folder 49)
- Quinn, Pat, 2000-2001 (Box 62, Folder 63)
- Quinlan, Shawn, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 55)
- Quisgard, Liz Whitney, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 56)
- Rabbath, Liane, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 57)
- Rabey, Svetlana, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 58)
- Rabinovich, Raquel, 1995-2001 (Box 43, Folder 59)
- Rachko, Barbara, 1995-2001 (Box 43, Folder 60)
- Raczka, Graegorz, 1999-2001 (Box 64, Folder 90)
- Radinovsky, Dean, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 61)
- Radloff, Nancy, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 62)
- Radsprecher, Carol, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Raff, Marcia, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Rafkin, Tamara, 2004 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Raimondi, John, 1995-2000 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Raimundi-Ortiz, Wanda, 2004 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Raissnia, Raha, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Rajakumar, Ravi, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Rajkovich, Jon, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Rakita, Robert M., 1972-1980 (Box 62, Folder 66)
- Ralph, David, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Ramella, Pablo, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Ramirez, Ricardo, 1993 (Box 62, Folder 64)
- Ramos, Juan, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 11)
- Ramsauer, Birgit, 1998-2001 (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Ramsay, Deb, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Ramsay, Lisa, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Ramsdell, Richard, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 15)
- Randall, Jill, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 16)
- Randall, Michael, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 17)
- Ranker, Marilyn, 1980-1983 (Box 62, Folder 65)
- Rankin, David, 2005 (Box 44, Folder 18)
- Raponi, Maria, 2005 (Box 44, Folder 19)
- Rappel, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 20)
- Rasch, Jody, 2005 (Box 44, Folder 21)
- Rasimus, John, 2005 (Box 44, Folder 22)
- Ratcliff, David, 2002 (Box 62, Folder 67)
- Ratcliffe, Oona, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 23)
- Rauam, Naima, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 24)
- Rauchman, James, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 25)
- Rauschenberg, Nisa, 1990-2001 (Box 44, Folder 26)
- Rauschenbusch, Stephanie, 1994-2001 (Box 44, Folder 27)
- Raviv, Ilana, 2005 (Box 44, Folder 28)
- Ray, Lynda, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 29)
- Ray, Vinnie, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 30)
- Raymond, Anna, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 31)
- Razavi, Valerie, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 32)
- Razin, Aleksandr, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 33)
- Read, Evan, 1996-2001 (Box 44, Folder 34)
- Reagh, Elizabeth, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 35)
- Records, Shawn, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 36)
- Reddig, Lisa, 2004 (Box 44, Folder 37)
- Reddy, Carolyn, 2005 (Box 44, Folder 38)
- Redwood, Deborah, 2005 (Box 44, Folder 39)
- Reed, Jesse F., 2005 (Box 44, Folder 40)
- Reed, Leslie, 2005 (Box 64, Folder 103)
- Reed, Patricia, 2000-2002 (Box 44, Folder 41)
- Reekers, Ronald, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 42)
- Rees, Sue, 1994-2001 (Box 44, Folder 43)
- Regan, Betsey, 1995-2001 (Box 44, Folder 44)
- Regehr, Duncan, 1995-2001 (Box 44, Folder 45)
- Reginato, Peter, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 46)
- Reich, James, 1997 (Box 64, Folder 50)
- Reichard, Deborah, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 47)
- Reichert, Herbert, 2005 (Box 44, Folder 48)
- Reichlin, Ann, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 53)
- Reid, Ian Marshall, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 52)
- Reid, Roy, 2005 (Box 44, Folder 51)
- Reiger, Christopher, 2002-2005 (Box 44, Folder 50)
- Reiland, Lowell, 1978-1987 (Box 62, Folder 68)
- Reiner, Louise, 1984-1986 (Box 62, Folder 69)
- Reingold, Babs, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 49)
- Reinhardt, Beatrix, 2001-2002 (Box 44, Folder 58)
- Reinhardt, Kimberly, 2005 (Box 44, Folder 57)
- Reiss-McCormack, Randi, 2005 (Box 44, Folder 56)
- Rembert, Cecelia, 2005 (Box 44, Folder 55)
- Renaldi, Richard, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 54)
- Render, J.A., 2003 (Box 44, Folder 59)
- Renes, Fernando, 2003 (Box 64, Folder 87)
- Renken, Constance, 2005 (Box 44, Folder 60)
- Rentz, Allison, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 61)
- Renvall, Seppo, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 62)
- Repasi, Ildiko, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Ress, Beverly, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Ress, Beverly, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Revis, Karen, 2000 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Reyna, Alexander, 2000 (Box 64, Folder 39)
- Reynolds, Gregory R., 1996 (Box 64, Folder 51)
- Rhodes, Matthew, 1998 (Box 62, Folder 76)
- Rhone, Joseph, 1998-2000 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Ricadonna, Laurie, 2005 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Ricci, Liane, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Rich, Michael, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Richards, Rosalyn, 2000 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Richardson, Teri, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Richardson, Willy, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 11)
- Riches, Gregory, 1992-2005 (Box 45, Folder 12)
- Richison, Michael, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 13)
- Richter, Ute, 1997-2001 (Box 64, Folder 41)
- Riedell, Steve, 2000 (Box 45, Folder 14)
- Riera, Antonia, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 15)
- Riina, Joanne, 2005 (Box 45, Folder 16)
- Riker, Maryann, 1992-1994 (Box 62, Folder 75)
- Riley, Brian, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 17)
- Riley, Charles R., 1983-1989 (Box 62, Folder 74)
- Riley, Duke, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 18)
- Riley, Elizabeth, 1989-2001 (Box 45, Folder 19)
- Riley, Rebecca, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 20)
- Rintel, Ruth, 2005 (Box 62, Folder 73)
- Rios, Diego, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 21)
- Rippens, Michael, 2000 (Box 45, Folder 22)
- Rito, Guillermo, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 23)
- Ritz, Lorna, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 24)
- Rivera, Bob, 1993-2001 (Box 45, Folder 25)
- Rizzi, JM, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 26)
- Robert Bell, Jason, 2003 (Box 62, Folder 72)
- Roberts, Darrell, 2005 (Box 45, Folder 27)
- Roberts, Karla, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 28)
- Roberts, Kristina, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 29)
- Roberts, Marie, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 30)
- Robertson, Elizabeth, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 31)
- Robinson, Andrew, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 32)
- Robinson, Caroleigh, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 33)
- Robinson, Danielle, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 34)
- Robinson, Dorothy, 2005 (Box 45, Folder 35)
- Robinson, Jack, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 36)
- Robinson, Kristine, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 37)
- Robinson, Maura, 1995-2001 (Box 45, Folder 38)
- Robinson, Zev, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Robinson, Zev, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 39)
- Robotham, Bradford, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 40)
- Robrish, Alice, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 41)
- Robson, Aurora, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 42)
- Rocco, Ron, 1993-2002 (Box 45, Folder 43)
- Rochette, Anne, 1986-1989 (Box 62, Folder 71)
- Rockwell, David, 2005 (Box 45, Folder 44)
- Rodburg, Rosalind, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 45)
- Rodriguez, Nicol, 1993-1994 (Box 63, Folder 25)
- Rodriguez, Ritchard, 1990-2005 (Box 45, Folder 46)
- Rodriguez, Tino, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 47)
- Rodwell, William, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 48)
- Rogers, Brenda, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 49)
- Rogers, Brooke, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 50)
- Rogers, Elizabeth, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 51)
- Rogers, Jenny, 2005 (Box 45, Folder 52)
- Rogowski, Kent, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 53)
- Rohlfing, Rita, 1993-1998 (Box 62, Folder 70)
- Rohrer, Jessica, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 54)
- Rojas, Ben, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 55)
- Rojas, Veronica, 2000-2001 (Box 45, Folder 56)
- Roleke, Margaret, 1994-2003 (Box 45, Folder 57)
- Romeo, Bea, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 58)
- Ronen, Gil, 2001 (Box 64, Folder 52)
- Roniger, Taney, 2005 (Box 45, Folder 59)
- Rooney, Autumn, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 60)
- Root, Matt, 2005 (Box 45, Folder 61)
- Rorandelli, Eva, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 62)
- Rosales, Mario, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 63)
- Rosania, MaryJo, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 64)
- Rose, Karen, 1989-1997 (Box 45, Folder 65)
- Rose, Roslyn, 1992-1994 (Box 62, Folder 77)
- Roselli, Grace, 2005 (Box 45, Folder 66)
- Roseman, Arlene, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 67)
- Rosen, Carol, 1990-1996 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Rosen, William, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Rosenberg, Laura, 1996-1999 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Rosenberg, Maddy, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Rosenberg, Michelle, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Rosemnblatt, Joshua, 1989 (Box 62, Folder 79)
- Rosenblatt, Phyllis, 1990 (Box 62, Folder 78)
- Rosenfeld, Lynn, 1989-2001 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Rosenwald, Laurie, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Rosier, Meredith, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Rosis, John, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Rosmarin, Cari, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Rosner, Adam, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 11)
- Roso, Marco, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 12)
- Ros Suarez, Moses, 1990 (Box 62, Folder 86)
- Ross, Catherine, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 13)
- Ross, Jana, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 14)
- Ross, Jennifer, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 15)
- Ross, Robin, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 16)
- Rosser, Phyllis, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 17)
- Rosshandler, Felicia, 1994-2001 (Box 46, Folder 18)
- Rossi, Steven, 2004 (Box 62, Folder 80)
- Rossof, Liz, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 19)
- Roth, Martin, 2003-2005 (Box 46, Folder 20)
- Roth, Ronald, 1991-1995 (Box 64, Folder 53)
- Rothenberg, David, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 21)
- Rothermel, Mary, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 22)
- Rothfeld, Michael, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 23)
- Rothman, Alicia, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 24)
- Rothschild, Jo Ann, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 25)
- Rothschild, Ruth, 1996 (Box 46, Folder 26)
- Roux, Barbara, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 27)
- Roux, Barbara, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 28)
- Rowland, Jake, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 29)
- Rowland, Sally-Ann, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 30)
- Roz, Emily, 1999-2003 (Box 46, Folder 31)
- Rozenman, Alexandra, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 32)
- Rozo, Arlene, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 33)
- Rubens, Nancy, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 34)
- Rubiku, Anila, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 35)
- Rubin, Allan, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 36)
- Rubin, Ben, 1996 (Box 64, Folder 54)
- Rubin, Susan, 1993 (Box 62, Folder 81)
- Rubinstein, Andrew, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 37)
- Rubirosa, Natasha, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 38)
- Rucker, Thomas, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 39)
- Ruda, Edwin, 1993-2001 (Box 46, Folder 40)
- Rudd, Timothy, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 41)
- Rudnik, Daniela, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 42)
- Rudolf, Colleen, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 43)
- Rudolph, Alena, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 44)
- Ruediger, John, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 45)
- Ruehlicke, Cornelia, 1990-2001 (Box 46, Folder 46)
- Ruff, Donna, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 47)
- Ruggiano, Maria, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 48)
- Rumbolo, Brian, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 49)
- Rundstrom, Lisa, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 50)
- Rupnow, Michiko, 1987-2000 (Box 46, Folder 51)
- Russel, Bailey, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 52)
- Russel, Silvia, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 53)
- Russell, Sara, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 54)
- Russell, Suzanne, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 55)
- Ruta = Loiseau, Francesca, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 56)
- Ruth, Tara, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 57)
- Ruzickova, Petra, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 58)
- Ryan, Michael, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 59)
- Ryan, W.Timothy, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Rybchynska, Larysa, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Saak, Eric, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Sabatino, Joseph, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 18)
- Sabharwal, Tara, 1991-2002 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Sabol, Lisbeth, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Saccaro, Claude, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Saccoccio, Jackie, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Sadauckas, Abby, 2005 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Sadeski, James, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Sadowski, Jenene, 2001 (Box 64, Folder 55)
- Safford, Alison, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- Saftien, Yutta, 1991-1998 (Box 62, Folder 85)
- Sage, Lu, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 11)
- Sagerman, Robert, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Saghatelian, Samuel, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 13)
- Sahni, S.K., 2003 (Box 47, Folder 14)
- Sahr, Ken, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 15)
- Saia, Jordan, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 16)
- Saiki, Katsuhiro, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 17)
- Sakellarion, Martha, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 21)
- Sakoff, Daniel, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 18)
- Saito, Kiyomitsu, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 20)
- Sakuma, Toshihiro, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 22)
- Salas, Haymee, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 23)
- Salerno, Kim, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 24)
- Salloum, Jayce, 1995-2003 (Box 47, Folder 27)
- Salinas Campo, Ignacio, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 26)
- Salmanson, Carol, 1999-2005 (Box 47, Folder 25)
- Salubayba, Don, 2005 (Box 47, Folder 28)
- Salvante, Mary C., 1998 (Box 64, Folder 56)
- Salvat, Jean-Daniel, 2005 (Box 47, Folder 29)
- Samaha, Sumayyah, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 30)
- Samant, Mohan, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 31)
- Samelson, Andra, 1994-2004 (Box 47, Folder 33)
- Samsara, Gregora, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 34)
- Samsel, Francesca, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 32)
- Sanae, Yasuda, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 35)
- Sananman, David, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 36)
- Sanchez, Eric, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 37)